semplicelabs.com 2016-11-25

# Semplice

## At Semplicelabs know that you expect privacy and security when it comes to information that personally identifies you and allows you to be individually contacted ("Personal Information").

### Why we request information about you

Semplicelabs collects and retains Personal Information about you only when you have communicated with us by email (we only collect your E-Mail address) and when you purchase a Semplice product (we'll ask for general information such as your name, email address, billing address, and credit card information). We use that information to transact business with you and deliver the requested products.

### Protecting your information

The information we receive from you is protected against unauthorized access once we receive it. We limit the access to your information to employees who have a business reason for accessing it. When collecting financial information from you, we use secure socket layer software (SSL). Despite our continual and evolving efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information. You acknowledge and agree that we make no such guarantee.

### Data Collected

We collect anonymous data from every visitor of the Website to monitor traffic and fix bugs. For example, we collect information like web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol address, the browser type, the browser language, and a timestamp for the request.

### Disclosure

We will not sell or distribute your Personal Information except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have permission, or it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. Business transfers If Semplicelabs, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Semplicelabs may continue to use the Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

### Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make major changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Product after such changes have been first posted. Questions on our privacy policy can be directed to hello@semplicelabs.com
